## Abhishek Kakar

Overall experience: 8+ years

C-201 Sahara Apartments Plot 11 | Sector 6 Dwarka New Delhi 110075

9004884446

kakar.abhishek@gmail.com

About me

A professional with experience in implementing and managing effective business processes. Highly astute, strong communicator and a talented professional, who can fit into roles like Sales Manager, Program Manager, Customer Success Manager, Operations Manager, Community Manager, Product Manager, Brand Manager etc.. Extensive understanding of the business ecosystem allows me to effectively manage remote/offline teams and deal with complex situations leading to a highly competent and growth focused environment.

**Work Experience** 

Sales Manager Great Learning, New Delhi June 2021 – June 2024

- Lead, mentor and motivate a team of sales professionals
- Develop customized sales pitches, training programs and presentations to unlock full potential of BDMs/SDRs
- Devise and execute strategic plans to achieve sales targets
- Conduct timely market research that includes the competitor analysis to improve the product
- Analyze complex data to identify and fix ground issues
- Work in synchronization with stakeholders (Product, Marketing and Operations team, University authorities etc.) to integrate strategies to develop and amend academic courses for Universities
- Set and track sales targets, monitor team performance and productivity and consistently meet revenue goals in accordance with organizational objectives
- Focus on Innovation and Creativity
- Manage the CRM system to optimize sales processes and funnel management
- Coach the team to maintain strong customer relations resulting in customer satisfaction and devise strategies to stop leakage
- Intervene at crucial junctures to enforce deal closures
- Conduct timely audit and training sessions for the team to improve performance

Sales Manager Young Solutions | New Delhi September 2017 – August 2020

Marketing and Sales Associate PricewaterhouseCoopers, New Delhi

November 2011 - April 2016

\_

## Skills and attributes

- Software proficiency: MS Word, Excel, PPT | Adobe Indesign, Illustrator, Photoshop
- Leadership acumen
- Sales acumen
- Persuasive
- Entrepreneurial outlook
- Adaptability
- Meticulous planning
- Strategic and Analytical
- Coaching and Mentorship
- Creative thinker and Problem solver
- Attention to detail and Process oriented
- Ability to manage remote/offline teams

—

## **Education**

## Post Graduate Diploma in Management (Sales and Marketing): 2020-2022

Maeer's Institute of Technology (MiT), Pune

**Graphics Design and Communications: 2007-2008** 

National Institute of Fashion Technology (NIFT), New Delhi

Diploma in French Language: 2006-2007

Alliance Francaise (AFD), New Delhi

Bachelor's of Arts (Political Science): 2003-2006

University of Delhi (DU), New Delhi

Higher & Senior Secondary School: 2001-2003

Cambridge School, New Delhi